Jeff Gold Collection ARC.0037
Library and Archives
- Series I: Artist Files, 1957-2004, undated
  - The Rolling Stones
    - Programs, 1972-1976
      - In concert program, 1969 (Box OS1, Folder 4)
      - US tour, 1972 (Box AF2, Folder 68, Object 13)
        A2004.54.85
  - Roxy Music, 1972-1979 (Box AF2, Folder 70)
  - Run D.M.C., 1991, undated (Box AF2, Folder 71)
    A2002.82.17a-A2002.82.17c
  - Rundgren, Todd, 1982 (Box AF2, Folder 72)
    contains one program
  - Russell, Leon, 1982 (Box AF2, Folder 73)
    A2002.82.15
  - Rydell, Bobby, 1962 (Box AF6, Folder 14)
    A2004.54.29
  - Sam & Dave, 1968, undated (Box AF3, Folder 1)
  - Santana, Carlos, undated (Box AF3, Folder 2)
  - Scorpions, 1980 (Box AF3, Folder 3)
    contains one tour program
  - Seal, 1999 (Box AF4, Folder 21)
    contains tour itinerary books
  - The Seeds, 1967 (Box AF3, Folder 4)
    contains one Fave magazine questionnaire filled out by Rick Andridge
    A2002.82.128
  - The Sidewinders, 1971 (Box AF3, Folder 5)
    contains one Max's Kansas City flyer
    A2002.82.45
  - Sims, Zoot, 1967 (Box AF3, Folder 6)
    contains correspondence re: tour dates
  - Sisters of Mercy, 1983 (Box AF3, Folder 7)
    contains one promotional pamphlet by Brain Eater record label
  - Small Faces, undated (Box AF3, Folder 8)
    A2002.82.203
  - Smith, Patti, 1976-1978, undated (Box AF3, Folder 9)
    contains fan club materials (including fanzines), and flyers
  - Spirit, undated (Box AF3, Folder 10)
  - Split Enz, undated (Box AF3, Folder 11)
  - Springsteen, Bruce, undated (Box AF3, Folder 12)
    contains one pamphlet for Springsteen's early band Steel Mill
  - Steeleye Span, c. 1973 (Box AF3, Folder 13)
  - Steppenwolf, undated (Box OS1, Folder 5, Box AF3, Folder 14)
    A2002.82.195, A2002.82.204, A2002.82.106-A2002.82.110, A2002.82.131
  - Steve Miller Band
    - The Joker promo, undated (Object Museum storage, Box OS1, Folder 5)
      A2005.105.43
      two copies
    - Greatest Hits album cover proofs, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-4, Object 23-28)
      six copies
  - Stevens, Cat (Yusaf Islam), 1974-1975, 1985, undated (Box AF3, Folder 15)
    A2002.82.199
    contains programs, letter from Yusaf Islam to Jeff Gold, and draft of an essay for the Islamic Society of North America
  - Stewart, Rod, undated (Box AF6, Folder 15)
    A2004.54.9
  - Sting, 1990 (Box OS1, Folder 5)
  - The Supremes, 1968 (Box AF3, Folder 16)
    contains one program (water-damaged)
  - T. Rex, 1974-1975, undated (Box AF3, Folder 17)
    contains one photocopied book chapter with editorial markings, and two issues of fanzine Electric Warrior
  - Talking Heads
    - Business card, circa 1976 (Box AF6, Folder 16)
      A2002.82.216
    - Memo from David Byrne, 1991 June 10 (Box AF6, Folder 16)
      A2004.54.20
  - Tangerine Dream, 1981 (Box AF3, Folder 18)
  - Taylor, James, 1976 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-5, Object 3-4)
    A2004.54.222a-A2004.54.222b
    In the Pocket album slicks (2 copies)
  - The Temptations, 1979 (Box AF3, Folder 19)
    contains one letter to Mo Ostin re: David Ruffin
  - Thin Lizzy, 1982 (Box AF3, Folder 20)
  - Tiny Tim, 1968, undated (Box AF3, Folder 21)
    A2002.82.114
  - Toussaint, Allen, undated (Object Museum storage)
    A2005.105.42
  - Traffic, 1967, undated (Box AF3, Folder 22)
    A2002.82.91, A2002.82.196
  - Triumvirat, undated (Box AF3, Folder 23)
    contains typewritten lyrics
  - U Boat, undated (Box AF3, Folder 24)
    Woody Woodmansey, lead singer; contains photographs and a promotional pamphlet
  - Ultravox, 1981 (Box AF3, Folder 25)
  - Uriah Heep, 1979 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-4, Object 2)
    A2002.82.202
  - Van Der Graaf Generator, 1975, undated (Box AF3, Folder 26)
    contains press kit with set list written on back page of pamphlet
  - Van Halen
    - General, undated (Box AF3, Folder 27)
      Includes handwritten note to 16 Magazine.
      A2004.54.25
    - Van Halen III release documents, 1997-1998 (Box AF3, Folder 28-29)
      originally housed in a three-ring binder
    - Tour itinerary books, 1993, 1995, 1998 (Box AF3, Folder 30-32)
  - The Velvet Underground, 1970-1971
    - Advertising documents for show at the Agora, Columbus, OH (Box AF3, Folder 33)
      A2002.82.43, A2004.54.137a-A2004.54.137g
    - General, 1970, 1974, undated (Box AF3, Folder 33)
  - Vicious, Sid, 1978 (Box AF3, Folder 34, Object Museum storage)
    A2006.4.1
    Contains clippings re: Nancy Spungen's murder, and one photograph.
    Photograph in Museum storage. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - Waits, Tom, undated (Box AF3, Folder 35)
    contains handwritten draft of Blue Valentine lyrics
  - Warrant, 1989 (Box AF3, Folder 36)
    A2002.82.156
  - Warwick, Dionne, undated (Box AF6, Folder 17)
    A2004.54.31
  - Waters, Muddy
    - Press kit, undated (Box AF6, Folder 18)
      A2004.54.18a-A2004.54.18b
    - Gravestone rubbings, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-4, Object 29-31)
  - Wells, Mary, undated (Box AF6, Folder 19)
    A2004.54.47
  - Werner, David, 1974-1975 (Box AF3, Folder 37)
    contains photocopied clippings
  - West, undated (Box AF3, Folder 38)
  - The Who
    - General, 1967-1975, 1981, circa 1982, undated (Box AF3, Folder 39)
      A2002.82.46, A2004.54.98, A2004.54.69a-A2004.54.69i, A2004.54.83, A2004.54.126a-A2004.54.126g
      Includes biography by Polydor Records, press kit for It's Hard LP, "Squeeze Box" sheet music, and press kit for Face Dances LP.
    - Photographs, undated (Object Museum storage)
      A2004.18.1-A2004.18.4
    - Tour program, 1967 (Box OS1, Folder 5)
      A2002.82.197
  - Williamson, Sonny Boy, 1965 (Box AF3, Folder 40)
    contains two pieces of correspondence re: royalties
  - Wilson, Jackie, undated (Box AF6, Folder 20)
    A2004.54.34-A2004.54.35
  - Wishbone Ash, 1972, undated (Box AF3, Folder 41)
    Includes flyers and a photograph.
    A2002.82.44, A2004.54.54
  - Womack, Bobby, 1968 (Box AF3, Folder 42)
  - Wonder, Stevie, 1986 (Box AF3, Folder 43)
    contains one tour itinerary book
  - Wood, Ron, 1979 (Box AF3, Folder 44)
    contains one biographical time-line
  - Wyman, Bill, 1974-1975 (Box AF3, Folder 45)
    A2002.82.82-A2002.82.83
  - The Yardbirds, 1965, undated (Box AF3, Folder 46)
    A2002.82.219
  - Yes, 1974 (Box AF3, Folder 47)
  - Zappa, Frank (and the Mothers of Invention)
    - Chunga's Revenge alternate album cover, 1970 (Object Museum storage)
      A2005.105.9
    - General, 1968, 1974 (Box AF3, Folder 48)
    - Hot Raz Time, 1973-1974 (Box AF3, Folder 48)
      A2004.54.55, A2004.54.101, A2004.54.120
      3 issues: Vol. 1 no. 6, 7, Vol. 2 no. 1
    - 200 Motels lobby cards, 1971 (Box OS1, Folder 5)
  - The Zombies, 2004 (Box AF3, Folder 49)
    contains one brochure for a tribute concert for Paul Atkinson
  - Various biographies, 1982-1985, undated (Box AF3, Folder 50)
    primarily documents artists not represented in this series
  - Various photographs, undated (Box AF3, Folder 51)
    documents artists not represented in this series; includes Eric Clapton, Cher, the Honeys, and Greene & Stone
    A2002.82.41, A2002.82.122
- Series II: Subject Files, 1938-2010, undated
  Series II: Subject Files complements the artist files by covering a similar time period, the 1950s through 2010. This series contains materials that document the larger music industry, including record companies and the people who worked for or with them. A secondary focus of this series is promotional materials, found in the form of flyers, handbills, postcards, and programs.
  - 93 KHJ Boss Radio reunion, 1990 (Box SF1, Folder 1)
    includes audio CD
  - The American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1959-1966 (Box SF1, Folder 2)
    photocopies of membership applications
  - American Music Awards script, 1986 (Box SF1, Folder 3)
    A2002.82.172
  - Bridges, Alvenia
    - Amnesty International tour, 1986 (Box SF1, Folder 4-5)
    - The Jimi Hendrix Exhibition, 1993-1994 (Box SF1, Folder 6)
    - The Rolling Stones documents, 1981-1983, 1989 (Box SF1, Folder 7)
    - U2 press conference documents, 1987 (Box SF1, Folder 8)
  - Broadside Records liner notes, 1963 (Box SF1, Folder 9)
  - Central Park concert series, 1967 (Box SF1, Folder 10)
    press releases
  - Classic Album Covers stamp set (British), 2010 (Box SF1, Folder 11)
  - Cohen, Kip, undated (Box SF1, Folder 12)
    photographs
  - Concert for Bangladesh press release, 1971 November 24 (Box SF1, Folder 13)
  - Decca-Coral Records, 1963-1968 (Box SF1, Folder 14)
  - Elektra Records, 1966-1972, undated (Box SF1, Folder 16-17)
    Includes Jac Holzman biography, advertising aids, catalogs, and newsletters.
    A2004.54.109, A2002.82.95-A2002.82.96, A2002.82.132, A2002.82.111,
  - Fender Album of Stars, undated (Box SF1, Folder 18)
  - Fields, Danny, 1971, 1975, undated (Box SF1, Folder 19)
    Contains two letters and an empty envelope.
    A2002.82.147a-A2002.82.147c, A2002.82.183
  - Film series brochures, undated (Box SF1, Folder 20)
  - Flyers
    see also file for General promotional materials
    - Agora (Columbus, OH), 1971, undated (Box SF1, Folder 21)
      Includes material related to John Lee Hooker, Howling Wolf, the Velvet Underground, Edgar Winter and White Trash, Lee Michaels, Chuck Berry, Albert King, Bob Seger, and Muddy Waters.
      A2002.82.16, A2002.82.22, A2002.82.42, A2002.82.43, A2002.82.92-A2002.82.94, A2002.82.126-A2002.82.127, A2002.82.157, A2002.82.159, A2004.54.3-A2004.54.4
    - Punk flyers, 1977-1989, undated (Box OS1, Folder 5, Object 1, Box SF1, Folder 22, Object Museum storage)
      Generation X and Roxy Club flyers on exhibit. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit for additional information.
      Artists include Cro-Mags, Dead Boys, the Dead Kennedys, Dickies, the Dictators, D.O.A., the Toy Dolls, and the Screamers.
      A2002.82.153-A2002.82.154, A2004.54.183-A2004.54.184, A2004.54.212-A2004.54.213, A2005.105.48-A2005.105.49, A2005.105.51-A2005.105.54, A2005.105.56-A2005.105.59
    - Shrine Exhibition Hall (Los Angeles), 1968 (Box SF1, Folder 23)
      Includes the Chambers Brothers, Chuck Berry, and Peter Green's Fleetwood Mac; and The Mothers of Invention (feat. Frank Zappa) with Charlie Musselwhite Blues Band and Sweetwater.
      A2001.93.26, A2004.54.11
      The item with Museum accession number A2001.93.26 is in Museum storage. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
    - Sing Out for Sight benefit, undated (Box SF1, Folder 23)
    - St. Bonaventure University, undated (Box SF1, Folder 24)
      A2002.82.160-A2002.82.161
    - La Cave, "Cleveland's House of Folk Music", 1967 January-1967 April (Object Museum storage)
      A2005.40.2
  - Folk
    - General, 1958, 1960, undated (Box SF1, Folder 25)
      A2002.82.221
    - Big Sur Folk Festival, 1970 (Box SF1, Folder 26)
    - Newport Folk Festival brochure, 1967 (Box SF1, Folder 25)
      A2004.54.14
  - "For an ideal collection", undated (Box SF1, Folder 27)
    record catalog of French releases by British and American groups
  - Gothic Music Calendar, 1999 (Box OS1, Folder 3, Object 1)
  - Handbills and postcards
    - ART: Artist Rights Today concerts, 1986-1987 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 1-3)
      Includes Jerry Garcia, Maria Muldaur, Country Joe, John Cippolina, etc. at the Fillmore (San Francisco); Maria Muldaur at The Stone (San Francisco); and Jesse Colin Young, John Cippolina, James Gurley, etc. at Club 9 (San Francisco).
      A2004.54.244-A2004.54.246
    - At the Gate: Certain Sounds plus Andre Hole, undated (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 4)
      A2004.54.60
    - The Band, Sons of Champlin, Ace of Cups, 1969 April 17-19 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 5)
      Location
      Winterland, San Francisco
      A2004.54.159
    - Big Brother and the Holding Company, 1968 April 11-13 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 6)
      A2004.54.155
      Fillmore, San Francisco
    - The Blues Project, Jimmy Reed, John Lee Hooker, and the Stu Gardner Trio, 1967 February 10-12 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 7)
      A2004.54.248
    - Lenny Bruce, and the Mothers of Invention, 1966 June 24-25 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 8)
      A2004.54.151
    - Tim Buckley, the Velvet Underground, and All Men Joy, 1968 July 19-21 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 9)
      A2004.54.236
      Avalon Ballroom, San Francisco
    - The Chambers Brothers with Buddy Miles Express and Sir Douglas Quintet, 1968 December 14 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 10)
      Swing Auditorium, San Bernadino, CA
      A2004.54.70
    - The Chambers Brothers, Quicksilver Messenger Service, 1967 April 7-9 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 11)
      A2004.54.153
    - The Doors, Captain Beefheart, and Lothar and the Hand People, 1967 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 12)
      A2004.54.238
      Denver, CO
    - The Doors and Procol Harum, 1967 November 16-18 (Box SF1, Folder 29, Object 1-2, Folder 58, Object 13)
      A2004.54.250
      Fillmore (11/16/67) and Winterland (11/17-18/67), San Francisco
    - Family Dog and the Common on the Great Hiway, undated (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 14)
      A2004.54.160
    - The Fillmore Summer Series, 1968 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 15)
      A2004.54.237
    - Friends and Relations - Free concert on the grass, undated (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 16)
      Perris Hill Park, San Bernadino, CA
      A2004.54.58
    - Grateful Dead and Miles Davis Quintet, 1970 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 17)
      A2004.54.17
    - Grateful Dead, Junior Wells, the Doors, Chicago Blues Band, 1967 January 13-14 (Box SF1, Folder 29, Object 3, Folder 58, Object 18-19)
      A2004.54.13, A2004.54.119
    - Grateful Dead with Paupers, 1967 May 5-6 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 20a-b)
      A2004.54.124a-A2004.54.124b
    - Rick Griffin Art Exhibition at the Roundhouse, undated (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 21)
      A2004.54.161
    - Hot Tuna, the Allman Brothers, Tripoli Steel Band, 1970 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 22)
      A2004.54.239
    - Iron Butterfly and the Velvet Underground, 1968 June 7-9 (Box SF1, Folder 29, Object 4, Folder 58, Object 23)
      A2004.54.247
    - Jefferson Airplane with the sights and sounds of the Trips Festival, 1966 February 4-6 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 24)
      A2004.54.150
    - Jethro Tull, Fairport Convention, Salt 'n Pepper and Clouds, 1970 April 30 - May 3 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 25)
      A2004.54.241
    - Little Richard, Joe Cocker, the Grease Band, and The Move, 1969 October 16-19 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 26)
      A2004.54.243
    - Miller Blues Band, Lee Michaels, and the Peanut Butter Conspiracy, 1967 February 10-11 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 27)
      A2002.82.180
    - Pink Floyd with Jeff Beck and Blue Cheer, 1968 July (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 28)
      Shrine Hall, Los Angeles
      A2004.54.84
    - Quicksilver Messenger Service with Final Solution, 1966 May 20-21 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 29)
      A2004.54.154
    - Otis Rush & His Chicago Blues Band, and The Mothers of Invention, 1967 March 3-5 (Box SF1, Folder 29, Object 8, Folder 58, Object 30)
      A2004.54.152
    - Spooky Tooth and the McCoys, 1968 September 27-29 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 31)
      A2002.82.194
      Grande Ballroom, Detroit
    - Summer of Love 20th Anniversary Concert, 1987 September 24 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 32)
      A2004.54.242
      Golden Gate Park, San Francisco
    - Vanilla Fudge and the Steve Miller Band, 1968 January 4-6 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 33)
      A2004.54.156
      Fillmore (1/4/68) and Winterland (1/5-6/68), San Francisco
    - The Who, 1967 June 16-17 (Box SF1, Folder 29, Object 9, Folder 58, Object 34)
      A2004.54.158
    - The Yardbirds and Country Joe and the Fish, 1966 October 23 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 35)
      A2004.54.157
    - The Yardbirds, It's A Beautiful Day, and Cecil Taylor, 1968 May 23-25 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 36)
      A2004.54.249
    - Frank Zappa and the Mothers of Invention, with Boz Scaggs, 1970 November 5-8 (Box SF1, Folder 58, Object 37)
      A2004.54.240
    - General, 1958-2005, undated (Box SF1, Folder 28-29)
      includes non-rock and roll
  - Historical materials, 1965-1974, undated (Box SF1, Folder 30)
    A2002.82.188, A2004.54.37
    Includes Easy Rider press kit, and a photograph of James Dean, by Phil Burchman.
  - International Artists record catalog, undated (Box SF1, Folder 31)
  - Invitations, 1968-1971 (Box SF1, Folder 32)
    includes invitation to a party for Derek Taylor
    A2002.82.191a
  - Island Records catalog, undated (Box SF1, Folder 33)
  - KRLA Beat, 1967, undated (Box SF1, Folder 34)
    A2002.82.176, A2002.82.88
  - NARM Convention, 1980 (Box SF1, Folder 35)
  - National Jazz and Blues Festival, 2004 (Box SF2, Folder 11)
    contains pages printed out from a website
  - Newspapers and magazines
    Includes clippings and complete issues
    - General clippings and complete issues, 1963-1976, undated (Box OS2, Folder 3, Box SF1, Folder 36)
    - 16 Magazine, 1973 May (Box SF1, Folder 36, Object 2)
      A2004.54.99
    - Blues & Soul Monthly Music Review, 1967 October (Box SF1, Folder 36, Object 1)
      A2004.54.108
    - Changes, 1971 March 1, December 1 (Box SF1, Folder 59, Object 1-2)
      A2004.54.117, A2004.54.130
    - Daily Mirror, 1964 May 18 (Box OS3, Folder 1, Object 1)
      A2004.54.179
    - Disc, 1963 August 24 (Box OS3, Folder 1, Object 2)
      A2004.54.215
    - Fusion, 1970 October 30 (Box SF1, Folder 59, Object 3)
      A2004.54.131
    - Jackie, undated (Box OS3, Folder 1, Object 5)
      A2004.54.216
    - Melody Maker, 1965 August 21 (Box OS3, Folder 2, Object 4)
      A2004.54.138
    - New Musical Express, 1964 December 25, 1965 July 2 (Box OS3, Folder 2, Object 2-3)
      A2004.54.218-A2004.54.219
    - Pop, 1973 (Box SF1, Folder 36, Object 3)
      A2004.54.116
    - Record Mirror, 1963 August 31 (Box OS3, Folder 2, Object 5)
      A2004.54.214
    - Record Retailer, 1965 August 19 (Box OS3, Folder 2, Object 1)
      A2004.54.217
    - Top Boys Photo News, 1964 April 4 (Box OS3, Folder 1, Object 4)
      A2004.54.220
    - Weekend and Today, 1967 August 30-1967 September 5 (Box OS3, Folder 1, Object 3)
      A2004.54.178
  - Newspaper concert ads - loose, 1968-1969, undated (Box SF1, Folder 37)
    A2004.54.64-A2004.54.68
    Includes Chuck Berry and Steve Miller Band at Fillmore West (San Francisco); Jackson Browne at "A Brotherly Benefit at the Magic Mushroom;" Moby Grape, Jeff Beck Group, and Mint Tattoo at Fillmore Carousel (San Francisco); and The Moody Blues, Frumious Bandersnatch, and Chicago Transit Authority at Fillmore West (San Francisco).
  - Personal, 1976-1988, undated (Box SF1, Folder 38)
    contains cards and newspaper clippings
  - Programs
    - General, 1969-1982 (Box SF1, Folder 39)
    - 1950s Rock & Roll Revival (Richard Nader), undated (Box SF1, Folder 40)
    - Benefit for NEST Foundation, 1988 Jan. 23 (Box SF1, Folder 57)
      A2004.54.224
      Featured artists
      Carlos Santana, Caribbean Allstars, Jerry Garcia, NRBQ, Bonnie Raitt, Boz Scaggs, and Tower of Power
      Oakland, CA
    - The Biggest Show of Stars for '57, 1957 (Box SF1, Folder 57)
      A2004.54.6
    - The Biggest Show of Stars for '63, 1963 (Box SF1, Folder 41)
    - Bottom Line, 1977 (Box SF1, Folder 42)
    - Farm Aid, 1985 (Box SF1, Folder 43)
      A2002.82.98
    - Grammy Awards, 1969 (Box SF1, Folder 44)
      A2002.82.99a-A2002.82.99b
      includes seating list
    - Hair (the musical), 1971 (Box SF1, Folder 57)
      A2004.54.8a, A2004.54.8c
    - Harmonyville Music Festival brochure, 1971 (Box SF1, Folder 57)
      A2004.54.97
    - Newport Folk Festival, 1967 (Box SF1, Folder 45)
    - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum grand opening gala, 1995 (Box SF1, Folder 46)
    - Summertime Open Air Festival, 1978 (Box SF1, Folder 47)
      A2002.82.207
  - Queen Booking Corporation family album, undated (Box SF1, Folder 48)
  - Ralph Records catalog, 1989 (Box SF1, Folder 49)
  - Reprise Records, undated (Box OS2, Folder 3)
    contains one empty 12 inch record sleeve
  - Rhythm & Blues Association of Great Britain, 1969 (Box SF1, Folder 50)
  - Rhythm N' Blues of 1956 printer plates (Box SF1, Folder 51)
    A2002.82.56-A2002.82.57
  - The Schaefer Music Festival in Central Park schedules, 1975-1976 (Box SF1, Folder 52)
  - Sheet music, 1977-1978 (Box SF2, Folder 12)
  - Sinclair, John, 1966, 1969 (Box SF1, Folder 53)
    A2002.82.185-A2002.82.186, A2002.82.142-A2002.82.146
  - Spin/Celluloid cassette advertisment, 1985 (Box OS2, Folder 3)
  - Stavers, Gloria, 1968-1996, undated (Box SF1, Folder 54-55)
  - That Was Rock press kit, 1984 (Box SF1, Folder 56)
  - Walden, Phil, 1963-1975 (Box SF2, Folder 1-2)
  - Warner Brothers Records, 1968-1973 (Box SF2, Folder 3)
    A2002.82.125
  - WDIA advertising documents, 1965 (Box SF2, Folder 13)
    Includes material on Barbara Lynn, Aretha Franklin, and B.B. King.
    A2004.54.134a-A2004.54.134c, A2004.54.135, A2004.54.136
  - Weberman, A.J., undated (Box SF2, Folder 4)
  - Woodstock, 1970 (Box SF2, Folder 5)
    A2002.82.187a-A2002.82.187b
  - WOR-FM 98.7 press kit for Murray the K and Scott Muni, 1966 (Box SF2, Folder 6)
    A2002.82.177a-A2002.82.177k
  - "World's Largest Selection of Oldies But Goodies" record catalog, 1966 (Box SF2, Folder 7)
  - Zines
    - Contagion, 1980-1981 (Box SF2, Folder 8)
    - Single issues, 1977-1985 (Box SF2, Folder 9)
  - General promotional materials, 1938-1982 (Box SF2, Folder 10)
- Series III: Art Collins Files, 1975-2005, undated
  Related Archival Materials
  Related materials providing content on Art Collins may be found in the following collections in this repository: Art Collins Papers.
  Series III: Art Collins Files documents 30 years (1975-2005) worth of Collins' work with the Rolling Stones and Iggy Pop. Of particular note in this Series are tour documents, including set lists, itineraries, contracts and riders, and statistics. In the Rolling Stones subseries, there is substantial information on royalties the band received in the early 1980s, as well as information about various recording sessions from that time. Both acts are well documented through photographs.
  - Subseries 1: General
    - Aircheck Factory, 1998-2000 (Box AC1, Folder 1)
    - Faithfull, Marianne, 1992-1995 (Box AC1, Folder 2)
    - Grammy Awards program, 1982 (Box AC1, Folder 3)
    - MTV Launch information, 1981 (Box AC1, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, 1982, undated (Box AC1, Folder 5)
    - Various artists and subjects, 1977-1995, undated (Box AC1, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Pop, Iggy
    - 2001 Fall tour documents (Box AC1, Folder 7)
    - Contracts and riders, 2001 (Box AC1, Folder 8-10)
    - Photographs, 1986; 1993-1998, undated (Box AC1, Folder 11-15)
    - R.O.A.R. tour documents, 1997 (Box AC1, Folder 16)
    - Tour itinerary books, 1991-2001 (Box AC1, Folder 17-19)
    - Various documents, 1987-2005 (Box OS1, Folder 5, Box AC1, Folder 20, Box OS2, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3: Rolling Stones Records
    - Atlantic Records bulletins, 1978-1979 (Box AC1, Folder 21)
    - Clippings, 1975-1986, undated (Box AC1, Folder 22-23, Box AC2, Folder 1-13)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1986 (Box AC2, Folder 14-19)
    - Invoices, 1979-1984 (Box AC3, Folder 1-5)
    - Let's Spend the Night Together, 1983 (Box AC3, Folder 6)
      press packet
    - Marketing, 1978-1985 (Box AC3, Folder 7-9)
    - Neville Brothers press packet, 1981-1982 (Box AC3, Folder 10)
      opening act on the Rolling Stones' 1981 tour
    - Photographs, 1979 (Box AC3, Folder 11)
    - The Rolling Stones
      Related Archival Materials note
      see Series II: Subject Files, Alvenia Bridges, for a file of documents on The Rolling Stones
      - 1978 tour documents (Box AC3, Folder 12)